

# Vicktor Lambok Desrony

Huta 1 , JL.Gereja T.Jawa +62 896-0109-2473 vicktordesrony@gmail.com

## **PROFILE**

Have experience as a Backend Developer. Have experience as a Project Manager in application development. Interested in studying the problems and providing solutions with ideas related to Information Technology. Able to work with teams or individuals and have good communication skills. Able to learn quickly about new things and are interested in learning new technology and other things about technology.

### Skills

Language

C/C++ , Java , PHP , HTML5 , CSS3, Javascript

Database & Server

MySql , Apache , Glashfish

Version Control

Git

#### **EXPERIENCE**

STUDENT TEACHING ASSISTANT - ITDEL(Sep 2020 – Dec 2020)
Student Teaching Assistant on Website Development Course
STUDENT TEACHING ASSISTANT - ITDEL(Jan 2021 – Present)
Student Teaching Assistant in Algorithm and Data Structure
Courses

STUDENT TEACHING ASSISTANT - ITDEL(Jan 2021 – Present) Student Teaching Assistant for Final Project 1 Course

PROJECT MANAGER(Jan 2020 – Jun 2020)

Project Manager & Programmer for the development of the Del Cloud Club web-based application

#### **EDUCATION**

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA (Sep 2019 – Sep 2022)

High School Diploma, Department of Information Technology Del Institute of Technology

#### **EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

DEL DATA SCIENCE CLUB (Nov 2019 - Present)

Del Data Science Club is one of the clubs that I joined on my campus, I got a lot of experience, additional knowledge and relationships here. I learned about Processing bulk data, processing data, and reusing data from Storage.

DEL PROGRAMMING CLUB (Jan 2020 - Present)

Del Programming Club is one of the clubs that I joined on my campus, I got a lot of experience, additional knowledge and relationships here. I learned a lot of efficient algorithms and problem solving here.

DEL MOBILE DEVELOPMENT (Mar 2021 - Present)

Del Mobile Development is one of the clubs that I joined on my campus, I got a lot of experience, additional knowledge and relationships here. I learned a lot of new things here, especially in pouring ideas into the form of applications that can be used to answer simple problems in everyday life.

#### WEBSITES & SOCIAL LINKS

https://www.linkedin.com/in/vicktor-desrony-1570911a5/

https://github.com/vldcreation